Viewers!
Right now, receive your faith and act now.
Ask Jesus to help you - to help your words and your thoughts.
In Jesus Christ's name.
To those in darkness - I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Darkness in your life - could be sickness, poverty, setback, depression -
be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
To those who are sick, afflicted - be free, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being free!
I can see you being healed!
Come out, in the name of Jesus!
To those in captivity - come out, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus, come out!
To those in captivity - come out!
Here is freedom; this is freedom.
Confess your freedom.
From captivity - confess your freedom.
Move - have freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to challenge your business for freedom.
My business, I challenge you - receive freedom!
I challenge your finances - receive freedom!
Receive breakthrough!
Receive freedom!
I challenge your marriage - freedom!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Where there is disunity - unity!
Peace in your marital life!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see peace.
I challenge your health - receive comfort!
In your blood, where there is pain - receive comfort!
Where there is discomfort - receive comfort!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be challenged, in the name of Jesus for freedom!
I am free!
This is what I'm hearing, "I am free!"
In Jesus' name.
CHALLENGE YOUR SITUATION FOR FREEDOM!!!
TB Joshua Prayer For Viewers
TT: Mel Flowers 29/06/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 08/07/2018